My name is Ilza.
My name is Hannah.
When I have other business to attend to,
these two will tend to your needs in my place.
Someone like me is being given
attendants? Two of them?
To be honest, I'm certain I'll
be too careful around them,
but this is common practice
among the aristocracy.
My name is Marie Shaderan.
I look forward to your kind assistance.
U-Um...
Might the two of you be
from the royal capital?
Yes. We are both born of knight's houses.
We've come here at the
recommendation of the third prince.
We've both served in the
royal palace, you see.
The royal palace? That's amazing!
Still, stories of the royal capital for
a noble such as yourself, Lady Marie...
They could hardly be novel
for you, could they?
Wait...
For some reason...
Lady Marie.
Perhaps you'd like your breakfast now.
Yes.
Episode 3 "A Life I Saw in a Dream, and a Dream-like Life"
I-Is this...
The appetizer is a charcuterie
assortment of seven items.
There is pork ham and sausage.
The terrine is pheasant.
The pâté de campagne is duck and venison.
Th-There are quite a lot of animals here.
We have prepared a number of
different dishes for you,
so please let me know which you prefer.
B-Both my palate and my stomach are lacking,
so I doubt I'll be
able to finish all of this.
You need only eat what you like. Please
leave anything you are unable to finish.
Oh, I couldn't! It would be such a waste!
Those are the master's orders.
Where is Lord Kyros now?
He is out on business.
Then, would you like half of—
A servant may not eat with their master.
There's nothing left for me to try.
This is delicious!
This is delicious, too!
My!
Fullness
URP
Lady Marie, you mustn't force yourself.
No, it's all delicious,
so I still have some room.
Probably.
Fullness
Please don't try to exceed your limits.
I'm so sorry. Those poor
ingredients. And the chef, too.
After you've rested a little,
I will show you around the palace.
You may find a change of clothes here.
I-It's incredible.
A-A magnificent sight.
But I only have one body.
I am aware.
In addition to these, there are others befitting
other seasons, over a hundred prepared in total.
A hundred?!
Please choose what you like.
What?
Something... I like.
Is there nothing here?
No.
They're all so lovely, I don't
know what I should choose.
Then let's settle on this one.
What?
It suits you very well.
Thank you.
Then, shall we?
Granado Castle was built
to protect the kingdom's borders
from the front lines during the war.
The House of Granado, margraves at the
time, constructed it to be a fortress.
If I recall, House Granado has
ties to the royal family, don't they?
Yes, but after the war, they attained the rank
of duke and now simply govern their own lands.
They are not in the line of succession.
Now, then.
This castle is used only
for special functions.
Lady Marie, let me show you to
the manor house where you will be residing.
Manor house?
We'll go through this door.
It's lovely!
This manor house was built
by Duchess Liu Liu.
The first floor houses the kitchen,
and also serves as a residence
for live-in staff.
There are also private rooms
for the duchess' family,
and facilities for entertaining
important guests.
Excuse me, it's Mister Tomas, isn't it?
I'm so sorry for my father's
inexcusably rude behavior.
My lady, how do you know my name?
I thought I heard someone call you by it.
You're right! That's my name!
That makes me sort of happy.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Marie Shaderan.
My name is Dibomov Tomas Tender.
Please call me Tomas.
Dibomov?
Are you named for the hero Dibomov
who discovered Louhav Island?
What?
I'm amazed you know about
him! I'm from Louhav Island!
My lady, you're incredibly knowledgeable!
Lady Marie is the master's fiancée.
Do not touch her without permission.
I apologize...
The castle was lovely,
but this room is wonderful, too.
I'm glad you like it.
Speaking of which, does Lord Kyros conduct
business with countries all over the world?
No. Essentially, he only trades
with the Ipsandros Republic.
I wondered because I saw folk crafts from
other countries all around the manor house.
Those are the servants' personal items.
Nations of Bandelee
Flaria
Other Countries
The head chef is from Flaria. The gardener
is from the Nations of Bandelee.
We have many nationalities here.
There's Tomas, for one,
but it's quite a diverse group, isn't it?
The master is perverse.
What?
In this kingdom, prejudice
is a matter of course,
but the master hires promising
individuals regardless of origin.
Which is why everyone
here is devoted to him.
I see. Mio, are you from the royal capital?
I was an abandoned child.
I'm told that I was left at a roadside inn.
I-I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
I've lived quite an enjoyable life.
When the master was little,
I used to comfort him.
Wait. How old is Mio?
As you can see,
many of us have difficult backgrounds,
but Ilza and Hannah are worthy
of being your attendants.
Both of them possess the dignity of
nobles born here in this kingdom.
I'd actually rather hear
stories of other countries.
Folk songs about old heroes,
learned by heart...
The call of an enormous bird with
rainbow-colored feathers...
But...
Thank you for going to
so much trouble for me.
I'll learn as much as I can so that
I don't embarrass any of you.
Your after-dinner tea.
M-May I have some milk?
Milk?
I often add milk to my black tea.
What do you add to your tea?
Milk in your black tea?
Doesn't that ruin the flavor?
What?
Putting cow's milk in tea?
What a novel way to drink it.
It's the first I've ever heard of it.
I'd expect nothing less of you, Lady Marie!
You're so free in your sensibilities.
It shouldn't be an issue in terms
of aristocratic etiquette.
Oh! Perhaps neither of them like milk!
I'm sorry. I don't think
I'll need any after all.
I'll drink it like this. Thank you.
Today was a long day.
I wonder if Lord Kyros is still
busy this late at night.
I wonder if Marie is enjoying herself.
Master,
tomorrow, you have a traders meeting in the
morning, a lunch meeting in the afternoon,
and following that, a market inspection.
When will I be able to go home?
〜A few days later〜
MUNCH
Breakfast today is large, as usual,
but the crisp juiciness of the
vegetables is so comforting.
Mio, where do you procure
these delicious vegetables?
They're from the vegetable
garden in the courtyard.
What?! There's a vegetable garden?
Yes. Johan works very hard at it.
I'd like to see the vegetable garden.
I'm sorry, but I must prepare
for the master's return.
Please take Ilza and Hannah with you.
I-I see.
I understand.
I hope this opportunity helps me
to grow closer to both of them.
I had no idea such a beautiful
vegetable garden was so close!
Hello.
Mister Johan, isn't it?
Hello. I hope you are well, my lady.
E-Excuse me, but...
those are tomato seedlings, aren't they?
Are you getting ready to plant them?
Y-Yes. This year's seedlings
have grown quite well.
Yes, it is that time of year, isn't it?
My lady, could it be...
that you've grown vegetables yourself?!
Y-Yes!
Cheap
It's less expensive than buying them,
Salable
and if there's extra, they can be sold.
Delicious
Simple
For a house as poor as ours,
our garden was a lifeline.
I see.
But tomatoes are susceptible to bugs and
disease, so they were difficult to grow.
Oh, yes. How far apart should
the seedlings be spaced?
Come this way. You can leave
the seedlings where they are.
You're going to show me? Oh, I'm so happy!
I don't believe it. She was
about to walk on the bare dirt.
Perhaps she isn't aware that gardens are
meant to be looked at and not walked in.
It's inconceivable. There are
bugs and that gardener in there.
Wait, perhaps the lady likes that.
Likes what? The bugs? The gardener?
Oh, you! I meant the bugs, obviously.
Of course. After all, no one
could possibly like that thing.
How can they be so rude?
I may be deserving of ridicule,
but Mr. Johan certainly isn't.
No, it isn't like that!
Wait!
These beautiful shoes were
given to me by the count.
I mustn't get these shoes dirty.
I know that.
Then, good night.
Yes, good night.
For some reason, I can't sleep.
Maybe I'll ask for some water.
Someone is awake.
Marie?
What's wrong? Can't you sleep?
U-Um...
I returned late, so I missed dinner.
Marie, please have a seat.
P-Pardon the intrusion.
It's been four days, hasn't it?
You've grown even more beautiful.
Not at all. I've been indulging myself
in the kindness of everyone here.
Marie, you're always like this.
My heart!
Apologies for the wait.
Oh! Toppo, you're still awake?
Welcome home, young sir.
Stare.
Let's see. I think Toppo is
the head chef, isn't he?
You asked for something light,
so this is chicken and cassava
in a salt-based soup.
Oh, it smells delicious!
Toppo, give Marie a serving, too.
Here you are.
Though I'm not sure it will
suit your tastes, Lady Marie.
I feel like he's being rather prickly.
This is delicious!
It's simple, but it has
such depth of flavor!
Toppo's cooking is delicious, isn't it?
Yes, it truly is! The food here
is always so delicious, I...
There's no need for polite flattery!
No, but I truly mean it!
No matter what I try, you never,
ever finish all your food! I understand!
It's because I, Toppo, lack the
skills! But the ingredients!
The meat and fish and...
I just feel so sorry for them!
Th-This is a misunderstanding! I don't
leave the food because it tastes bad!
What?
I felt badly for wasting
all those ingredients, too!
But...
Mio, didn't you ask Marie what she liked?
Whether it's food or dresses, Lady Marie is
unable to say that she dislikes something.
N-No, all of it truly has been delicious!
There wasn't anything that I disliked!
My lady, is that true?
It's true! I got full and couldn't
eat anymore, that's all!
Then you were pleased with
the food? I'm so glad!
M-Mio, what should I do?
I'll go make some tea to end your meal.
What?!
Marie, don't worry.
Toppo is always quick to cry.
Is he?
I, Toppo, had no idea that my
lady felt that way, and yet I...
I will pull myself together
and bring your dessert!
Now, here you are!
It's incredible!
How many apples did it take?
The reason it didn't occur to Toppo
I'll portion it out for you!
is that he doesn't understand that
others can't eat as much as him.
Let's all eat it together, Toppo.
What?! You wouldn't mind?
Of course not.
Ended up
eating half
Well then, I shall take my leave!
A good night to you both!
Yes. Thank you, Toppo.
Please get some rest.
I'm sorry, Marie.
What?
I created a situation that forced you
to consider others first.
Is there anything besides the
food that you've found trying?
Oh, no. Everything is so wonderful
it seems a shame to waste it on me.
What about Ilza and Hannah?
They take good care of me.
A friend of mine recommended them to me.
You are a future duchess.
I want you to be received in a
manner that befits that station.
Thank you.
They really are treating me well.
Marie, your habit of enduring
unpleasantness is a dire one.
What?
Just because someone is treating you well
doesn't mean that you're
obliged to be happy about it.
And if you aren't happy about
it, then you can just tell me.
I don't have any preferences.
No. I don't understand what
it means to pick what I like.
I did the work that needed to be done
and accepted what was given to me.
That was enough.
It can't possibly be all right for
me to choose based on my feelings.
I'm sorry, Lord Kyros. I don't want to
squander a single one of your kindnesses.
Marie, if you lack for something, tell me.
I will give you everything you want.
Something I lack?
There shouldn't be anything, and yet...
Pardon me for interrupting
your conversation.
Oh! I see you've brought
something very nice!
Something nice?
Then please relax and enjoy.
Piled High
It's so big! Is that Mio's late-night snack?
Marie.
Do you know what this is?
N-No. It's the first time I've seen one.
It's called a çaydanlik, and it's
used to make tea in Ipsandros.
First, you light the bottom
section to boil the water.
The heat of the water rises upwards,
slowly steaming the tea leaves
and bringing out their flavor.
When the time is right, you pour hot water
from the bottom pot into the top pot,
then place the pots back in their
original positions and wait.
When the tea is ready,
you use the remaining hot
water to dilute it to taste.
So everyone can adjust it to
their preferred strength!
Tea is Ready
Everyone gathers around the
pot, waiting for it to brew.
They ask each other's preferences
and grow closer to one another.
So then, Marie...
please tell me about yourself.
O-Of course.
Tell him about me.
But what should I tell him?
I've never experienced
anything fun in my life!
Marie! Marie!
What do you want to play?
I want to play...
Word-chains!
Lord Kyros, let's play word-chains!
Stunned
Word-chains?
Why would someone in his exalted
position play word-chains?!
Count
24 year-old
Ultra Wealthy
What a childish thing to think
of. I'm so embarrassed!
In order to enjoy a game
of word-chains at our age,
we'll need to add a little something.
Let's focus on areas where
our knowledge overlaps.
What? I-In that case, what about
things you like, Lord Kyros?
All right. It's limited
to things that we like!
Is it all right if I start?
O-Of course!
Then here I go!
Marie!
Wha—
Don't you usually start with "A"?
In that case, apple pie!
"E"... Something I like...
Exciting Ipsandrian stories!
You said the same thing
that night, didn't you?
I did!
You should visit the
castle library sometime.
I'm certain it's full of
things you'll love, Marie.
Yes, I will. Thank you.
Next is the "s" from "stories." "S"...
Sweet ricotta cheese!
"E"... Early zucchini!
Iconic gnocchi!
Inexpensive carrots!
Simple tompouce cakes!
Sweet potato!
Opulent chocolate truffles!
Stalks of rice.
Elegant soufflé.
Early lettuces.
"S"... "S"...
Stroopwafel.
Looseleaf rooibos.
"S" again?!
"S"... "S"... There aren't any more.
S-Sponge cake stack.
Lord Kyros, you've only been naming sweets!
What about you, Marie?
You're only listing agricultural goods!
What? W-Well...
Vegetables grow large very
quickly, so they're economical,
and they're delicious in many recipes.
That's so like you, Marie.
Honestly.
Sorry. I'm sorry. Forgive me.
Come on. Next is "K."
Something I like that starts with "K"...
Kyros.
I feel like I heard something
that ends in "S."
I-I said, "kiss."
I see. I see. So, Marie, you like kisses.
Oh, that isn't what I meant!
Hmm. But "S" again, is it?
Souvenirs by area!
Aromatherapy!
You, Marie!
Oh, honestly! This person
is really just too much!
You're still playing?
Mio.
The tea...
is cold, isn't it?
Oh.
It's no good.
It's bitter because it's over-brewed.
Let's sweeten and mask
the flavor with milk and sugar.
I don't believe the two of you
require any further sweetness.
Mio!
She's already gone!
Lady Marie doesn't believe the
master feels the way he does.
She doesn't feel she can truly
settle into life at the castle.
But I think I understand a
little of how she feels.
After all, I was once
in a similar situation.
Next Time, "I've Found the Things I Like".
Episode 4 "I've Found the Things I Like."
You know what will happen to you
if you don't watch, don't you?